(Amy:)Then people sit
(Amy:)on opposite sides of the table
(Amy:)and try to blow the wool off.
(Dr Koothrappali:)Sorry.
She's taken, too.
(Howard:)You know what I think
your problem is?
(Howard:)You're jealous
(Howard:)because you and I
used to be
(Howard:)best friends until
Koothrappali came along.
(Leonard:)And you found somebody
you could push around?
Hey!
Stay out of this.
(Leonard:)Okay.
(Howard:)You know, maybe I'm
best friends with Raj
(Howard:)because he doesn't think
he's smarter than me.
(Raj:)Actually...
I said, stay out of it!
N-No. No, Raj, go ahead,
say what you were gonna say.
(Raj:)All I'm gonna say is
(Raj:)you guys need
to stop this right now.
It-It's bad enough that
my parents are fighting,
(Raj:)now I have to hear
the two of you?
(Raj:)And who cares who's smarter?
(Raj:)If it's Leonard or me or...
(Raj:)you know, it's Christmas,
let's say it's Howard.
(Howard:)Well, if you're so smart,
you get the bird out.
(Raj:)No, you're the one
who let him in.
(Howard:)How do you know
it wasn't Leonard?